Aren't you too nervous?
あんまり緊張しないですか?
Yes, I'm nervous.
はい、緊張します
I wonder if I can wear simple clothes?
シンプルな服を穿えそうなのかな?
Just sandals?
サンダルだけ?
Just sandals.
サンダルだけ
Well, let me take it off right away.
じゃあ早速脱いでもらおうかな
Now, let's turn around.
じゃあ後ろ向いてもらおう
kana.
かな
Isn't it cold?
寒 くない?
Well then, one more time.
じゃあもう一回
So can I have you take the plastic?
じゃあプラを取ってもらっていい?
yeah?
ん?
Is it shaved?
パイパンかな?
ERROR
答え言わないでよ
Well then, shall I take off my pants?
じゃあ パンツ脱いちゃおうか
Belly buttoned?
おへそむき?
picture?
え?
Do you want to crush it?
つぶったい?
ERROR
あ、すごいつぶったい
Nip Neg.
ニップネグ
My hands are a bit cold.
ちょっと俺手冷たいから
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Well then, could you please put your left foot on this area?
じゃあ、この辺に左足乗せてもらっていいかな
ERROR
両手でおまんこ広げてね
So next time, I'll be here with my fourth eye and butt,
じゃあ今度は、ここに四つ目になってお尻つきやして、
On that side.
あっち側で
Wow that's amazing.
わーすごい
Shall I open my legs again?
もう一度足開いちゃおうか
Now put it on your chest, then turn your right hand from the outside,
じゃあ今度胸つけて、 じゃあ右手を外から回して、
Spread your pussy like this.
こうやっておまんこ広げて
ERROR
よし、じゃあシャワー浴びよっか
Well then, take a quick shower.
じゃあ、ちょっとシャワー出してって
Should I close this?
これ閉める?
Yeah.
うん
This is probably the correct way to go.
これが多分、ちゃんとはこうだから
Is that quite enough?
結構あれ?
It's lukewarm.
ぬるいな
Nuine.
ぬいね
Was it happening?
あ てはなってた?
Isn't it happening?
なってないか?
It was.
なってた
Okay, this.
いいよ、これ
yes.
はい
Huh?
えっ?
There it is.
あっつ
What happened?
どうしたんですか?
This will catch your eye.
これが目をつけるよ
There it is.
あっつ
Are you going to watch it a lot?
結構見ちゃう?
How many?
何本?
In Japan.
日本で
Yours?
あんたの?
How many times did you hear that voice earlier?
さっきの声は何回してるの?
I won't shut up for a moment.
ちょっと黙らないです
Oh, really?
あ、ほんと?
Do I have to do it today?
今日はしなくていいですか?
You don't have to.
しなくていいよ
Don't you know?
お前にとか知らない?
I know.
知ります
Oh, don't you know?
あ、知らないですか?
I don't know.
知らないです
Don't you know?
お 前 にとか知らないですか?
I don't know.
知らないです
Oh, I don't know.
あ、知らない
About you.
お前のこと
Oh, a toy?
あ、おもちゃ?
What kind of toys do you have?
どんなおもちゃを持っているの?
I don't know.
知らないです
yeah?
ん?
I don't know.
知らないです
Don't you know?
知らないですか?
phone, website, etc.
電話とか、サイトとか
What kind of toys do you have?
どんなおもちゃを持っているの?
I don't know.
知らないです
Is Sexchu better than Raku?
セクチューは楽より?
I have it many times.
何回でも持ってます
Bring your mouth open?
口を開けてもたらる?
Thank you.
ありまして
Won't you sit down?
座らないの?
結構
yeah?
ん?
It was Mando.
たまんどだったの
Ma-chan, are you going to sleep?
まーちゃん、寝る?
sleep.
寝る
Okay.
よし
It's dangerous, so I'm going to sleep.
危ないから、寝る
Oh, my goodness.
あ、まーまー
Oh my.
まーまー
I'm sweaty.
汗いね
After all, it was about 38 degrees.
だって、これ38度くらいだったの
Oh, is it the other way around?
あ、逆か
Because the yellow one didn't arrive.
だって、黄色のほうが届くなかったの
I see, I see.
そうか、そうか
Like there's a red line.
赤い線があるように
Before, there were ordinary people in the 2nd ward.
前、2区に常人がいたんだよね
I don't know if it's related.
関係あるか分からないけど
I see.
なるほど
But I've been waiting a long time.
でも、結構待ってたから
Yeah.
うん
Somehow,
なんか、
There's a part of me that's pulling at me.
ヘ ラの、自分の中の引っ張っている部分がある
strong.
強い
Huh, what is it?
え、なんだろう?
It broke.
壊れちゃいました
I deleted it though.
消したんだけどな
Shall I leave my towel over there?
気のタオル、そっち置いておこうか
Well then, just a moment.
じゃあ、ちょっと
Well...
え っとね
I'll be living here, so I guess I'll give it a try.
ここで俺が住まるから、ヘラしてもらおうかな
It might be a little difficult to do.
ちょっとね、やりづらいかな
Good.
よいしょ
After all, while looking at the camera.
やっぱ、カメラ見ながらね
What are you talking about?
何喋ってんの?
what?
何?
dazzling?
眩しい?
Progress steadily.
どんどん進歩する
That's amazing, so erotic
すごいね、エロい
hey.
ね
There was a back there.
奥 があったんだけど
Will this progress reach us?
この進歩、届く?
Back.
奥
Well, I think it'll arrive.
ね、届きそう
So, are the balls good?
じゃあ、玉いい?
Tie it, pull it, and pull it with your mouth.
結んで、引っ張って、口で引っ張る感じで
It's really a ball.
ほんと、玉ね
Really, like that.
ほんと、あんな風に
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are your hands sticky?
手とかベタベタになってない?
Yeah, it's okay.
うん、大丈夫
The floor has become sticky.
床がベタベタになってきた
Yes, that's right.
うん、そうだね
Hey, come on, sit on the couch.
ちょっとじゃあ、君、ソファに座ってて
Do you have any hobbies?
なんか趣味とかある?
Is it your hobby?
趣味ですか?
ah.
ああ
Like alcohol.
酒みたいな
Oh, really?
あ、そう?
Is it okay to remember?
思い出すとダメですか?
After you wake up?
起きてから?
After I woke up.
起きてから
Wow, that's amazing.
え、すごい
I've already forgotten.
もう忘れてる
Sister, don't give me a little extra.
お姉ちゃん、ちょっとプラスないで
Quickly add to small areas of hair.
髪の毛の小さなところにスピーディーにプラス
Ah, amazing.
あ、すごい
A little bit of extra goes a long way.
ちょっとのプラスで結構なる
Wow, that's amazing.
え、すごい
Oh, sorry.
あ、すみません
So, raise your eyes.
じゃあ、両目で上げて
I'll take it off.
外すよ
And you'll see it.
で、見えてくるでしょ
Around here in the back.
後ろこの辺に
Yeah, I haven't brought it yet.
うん、 まだ持ってきてない
It's here.
来た
It's hard to put the camera down.
カメラ置く大変
Press your feet and bring the edge back.
足を押して、縁を持ち返す
Good.
よいしょ
dangerous.
危ない
Then, put your hand between your legs.
で、手を足と足の間から通して
I might try expanding it a little myself.
自分でほんのく広げてみようか
Oh, that's amazing.
お、すごい
Yeah.
うん
Zalzal.
ザルザルして
put out?
出す?
Oh, this place is amazing.
あ、すっごいここ
Make a lot of noise.
すっごいザルザルして
Ah, I kinda got it right.
あ、ちょっと当たった
It's quite deep, really.
結構奥だ、ほんと
Hey.
ね え
Ah, sensitive.
あ、敏感
amazing.
すごい
You're sensitive.
敏感じゃん
Do you have something like this?
こういうの持ってんの?
Yeah.
うん
Yes, that body is amazing.
うん、やっぱりその身体はすごい
Yeah.
うん
I'm doing it.
やって るわね
Yeah yeah.
うんうん
picture?
え?
Properly.
ちゃんと
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
a.
あ
picture?
え?
a.
あ
Take a look.
見てみて
a.
あ
Hmm.
うーん
How many times did I say it?
何回ぐらい言ったかな?
How many times?
何回ぐらい?
Mmm, delicious.
うーん、おいしい
It's close.
近いわ
Here you go.
さあ、どうぞ
picture?
え?
Uho.
うほ
Can you say it?
言える?
Are you brave?
勇気ある?
picture?
え?
I can't say it.
言えない
Can't you say it?
言 えない?
But it's scary.
でも怖いね
I like that your voice is hollow.
声がかぼそくていいね
It's pumpkin.
かぼそくね
How to cradle it.
あやぎ方が
Maybe you can see it.
見えるかもね
Yeah yeah.
うん うん
I'm getting hungry.
お腹が空いてきた
Yeah.
うん
Not much.
あ んまり
A little.
ちょいな
Wait a minute.
ちょ いちょいちょい
Okay.
よし
Well then, ah, like this.
じゃあ、あ、こう
Upwards?
上向き?
How old is Atai?
あったいって何歳?
Middle aged 6 years old.
中年6歳
oh.
おー
Like middle and high school.
中高校ったい
Did you know this time?
この頃はお前は知ってた?
I knew.
知ってた
Um, college student, did it feel good?
あのー、 大学生、気持ちよかった?
Didn't you say that?
言いなかった?
But it was fun, you wanted to do it?
でも楽しみだったんだよね、やりたかった?
I was looking forward to it, but I felt like it was something like this.
楽しみだったけど、なんか、こんなものかみたいな
Ah, well, maybe so.
あー、まあ、そうかも
I went to university for the first time at the age of 7.
初大学7歳ね
Middle school, 5 years old.
中、5歳
oh.
おー
Middle school or high school student?
中、高校生?
Who was it?
誰だったの?
Hayashi.
はやし
Did you know at that time?
その頃はお前に知ってた?
I knew.
知ってた
Um, how have you been lately?
あのー、 最近はどうだった?
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Hmm, a lot.
うーん、いっぱい
Didn't you say that?
言いなかった?
But it was fun, you wanted to do it?
でも楽しみだったんだよね、やりたかった?
Ah, maybe so.
あー、そうかも
Were you holding back your voice?
声我慢してた?
I was holding back.
我慢してた
Hmm, that's terrible.
う ーん、やばいね
Are you excited?
興奮した?
Hmm, make sure it's snug.
うーん、 ぴっちりしてね
Did it hurt?
痛かった?
Tell me.
言ってね
Ah, it's already getting really intense.
あー、もうぎゅんぎゅんなっちゃってんじゃん
Hold both legs.
両足抱えて
Oh, so many things.
おー、いろいろ
Next time, raise your butt and let me pull this.
今度、お尻上げて、これ引かせてね
Yeah.
うん
oh.
おー
Did you see this?
お前、これ見えた?
It's noisy outside.
外、うるさいね
What are you doing?
何やってんの?
Yeah.
うん
Ah, that hurts.
あー、痛い
Will this become an unnecessary situation?
今度、余計な場合になっちゃうか
Oh, so many clips, so many clips.
あー、クリップいっぱい、クリップ
Awesome, amazing.
すごいすごい
It's so erotic.
めちゃくちゃエロい
Just a little more, that's fine.
もうちょい、だしら、いいじゃん
ah,
あー、
Are you feeling exhausted already?
もう ぎゅんなっちゃう?
Really erotic.
本当に、エロい
Wait, it's already been half a year since I've been preparing?
もう、ちょっと、おうけいが準備半年?
Is it not yet?
まだかな?
Shall we take a little break?
もう少し休憩しようか
Can you beg?
おねだりできる?
Begging?
おねだり?
Where?
どこに?
Please put it in mank.
マンクに入れてください
Don't call it symposium.
シンポって言うな
Then let's put it in.
じゃあ入れちゃお
I'm really nervous.
すごいビクビクしてる
This is crazy.
これヤバイやつだ
Highest.
最高
can?
できる?
Can you do it while kissing?
キスしながらできる?
amazing.
すごい
Yeah.
うん
ah.
ああ
Highest.
最高
ah.
ああ
Shall I take this out then?
じゃあこれ抜いちゃうか
Pull it out.
抜いて
On the contrary, pull it out.
反対に抜いて
Oh, that's crazy.
ああ、ヤバイ
ah.
ああ
ah,
ああ、
amazing.
すごい
Wow, the payment effect is paying off.
すごい、 支給効果渡ってるね
Oh, it hurts, it hurts.
ああ、痛い痛い
Highest.
最高
Shall we add a little more?
もうちょっと足しようか
cormorant
う
Hmm.
ーん
there were?
あ った?
Is it correct?
当たってる?
That's right.
当 たってる
Even my favorite child.
好きな子もね
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Tell people who are watching that Shinpo is the best.
見てる人に シンポ最高ですって言って
Shinpo is the best.
シンポ最高です
Thank you for your patience.
しこっていただいてありがとうございます
Thank you for coming out.
出ていただいてありがとうございます
Wow, water surface mancoba.
わあ、水面マンコーバ
Wow, it's here.
わあ、出た
Hold me down a little.
ちょっと押さえてて
Has it gone up?
出てんの上がった?
It came out quite deep.
結構奥で出した
Has it gone up?
出てんの上がった?